{
    "id": "dee320197efe4380a0acf226b837d3fd",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Iron ………………….. in many countries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "found",
                "is found"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4fd5e3e8e0b64403b9be07465a123b9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wondered how ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it is made",
                "was it made",
                "it was made"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc700ffe2fd9468689ce2caa8815141d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The university ………………… in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was found",
                "was founded",
                "found"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7955e82d794f4cbbaaf404a3303904dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can …………………… this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "avail",
                "avail of",
                "avail yourself of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dfcf2803d9494b548068c4eb490410aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ………………….. sorry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f0596a045c76452eab3d61574dab4bd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………. to invite me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very kind",
                "very kind enough",
                "kind enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e46aa60f820340a6b4e90662564f46e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told the story …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in details",
                "in detail",
                "with details"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c6c8fc246a9c4eeb8d8c7d7406acbeef"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. there was no one there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Before long",
                "Long before",
                "Long ago"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7618cc9a91ca40a3b0fb8d7975925e52"
        },
        {
            "question": "This book is ………….. interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "524ce325a56440cc9470c4cc8b07460b"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… such a sight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Never I have seen",
                "Never have I seen",
                "Never I saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65d1d691fc4841d9ba5e9e08dd2c5336"
        }
    ]
}